Alice B-PER
met O
the O
Queen B-PER
in O
Wonderland B-LOC

The O
Hatter B-PER
visited O
London B-LOC

The O
Duchess B-PER
spoke O
to O
Alice B-PER

Alice B-PER
followed O
the O
White B-PER
Rabbit I-PER

The O
Queen B-PER
ruled O
Wonderland B-LOC

The O
King B-PER
sat O
beside O
the O
Queen B-PER

Alice B-PER
walked O
through O
Oxford B-LOC

The O
Caterpillar B-PER
asked O
Alice B-PER
a O
question O

The O
March B-PER
Hare I-PER
joined O
the O
Hatter B-PER

Alice B-PER
remembered O
Dinah B-PER

The O
Gryphon B-PER
and O
the O
Mock B-PER
Turtle I-PER
talked O

Wonderland B-LOC
confused O
Alice B-PER

The O
Rabbit B-PER
ran O
to O
the O
court O

Alice B-PER
left O
Wonderland B-LOC
for O
London B-LOC

The O
Queen B-PER
shouted O
at O
the O
Hatter B-PER

Dinah B-PER
was O
Alice B-PER
's O
cat O

The O
Duchess B-PER
lived O
near O
Wonderland B-LOC

Alice B-PER
found O
the O
Cheshire B-PER
Cat I-PER

The O
Cheshire B-PER
Cat I-PER
smiled O
at O
Alice B-PER

Oxford B-LOC
was O
far O
from O
Wonderland B-LOC

The O
White B-PER
Rabbit I-PER
carried O
a O
watch O

Alice B-PER
saw O
the O
March B-PER
Hare I-PER
in O
Wonderland B-LOC

The O
Mock B-PER
Turtle I-PER
sang O
to O
the O
Gryphon B-PER

London B-LOC
and O
Oxford B-LOC
are O
places O

The O
Queen B-PER
of O
Hearts I-PER
called O
Alice B-PER

Alice B-PER
listened O
to O
the O
King B-PER
of O
Hearts I-PER

The O
court O
was O
in O
Wonderland B-LOC

The O
Hatter B-PER
drank O
tea O
with O
Alice B-PER

The O
Duchess B-PER
met O
the O
Cheshire B-PER
Cat I-PER

Alice B-PER
dreamed O
about O
Wonderland B-LOC
