“ O
you O
might O
just O
as O
well O
say O
that O
‘ O
i O
see O
what O
i O
eat O
’ O
is O
the O
same O
thing O
as O
‘ O
i O
eat O
what O
i O
see O
’ O
! O
” O
“ O
you O
might O
just O
as O
well O
say O
, O
” O
added O
the O
march B-PER
hare I-PER
, O
“ O
that O
‘ O
i O
like O
what O
i O
get O
’ O
is O
the O
same O
thing O
as O
‘ O
i O
get O
what O
i O
like O
’ O
! O
” O
“ O
you O
might O
just O
as O
well O
say O
, O
” O
added O
the O
dormouse B-PER
, O
who O
seemed O
to O
be O
talking O
in O
his O
sleep O
, O
“ O
that O
‘ O
i O
breathe O
when O
i O
sleep O
’ O
is O
the O
same O
thing O
as O
‘ O
i O
sleep O
when O
i O
breathe O
’ O
! O
” O
“ O
it O
_is_ O
the O
same O
thing O
with O
you O
, O
” O
said O
the O
hatter B-PER
, O
and O
here O
the O
conversation O
dropped O
, O
and O
the O
party O
sat O
silent O
for O
a O
minute O
, O
while O
alice B-PER
thought O
over O
all O
she O
could O
remember O
about O
ravens O
and O
writing O
- O
desks O
, O
which O
wasn O
’ O
t O
much O

alice B-PER
was O
rather O
doubtful O
whether O
she O
ought O
not O
to O
lie O
down O
on O
her O
face O
like O
the O
three O
gardeners B-PER
, O
but O
she O
could O
not O
remember O
ever O
having O
heard O
of O
such O
a O
rule O
at O
processions O
; O
“ O
and O
besides O
, O
what O
would O
be O
the O
use O
of O
a O
procession O
, O
” O
thought O
she O
, O
“ O
if O
people O
had O
all O
to O
lie O
down O
upon O
their O
faces O
, O
so O
that O
they O
couldn O
’ O
t O
see O
it O
? O
” O
so O
she O
stood O
still O
where O
she O
was O
, O
and O
waited O

she O
was O
walking O
by O
the O
white B-PER
rabbit I-PER
, O
who O
was O
peeping O
anxiously O
into O
her O
face O

he O
looked O
at O
alice B-PER
, O
and O
tried O
to O
speak O
, O
but O
for O
a O
minute O
or O
two O
sobs O
choked O
his O
voice O

“ O
— O
and O
just O
take O
his O
head O
off O
outside O
, O
” O
the O
queen B-PER
added O
to O
one O
of O
the O
officers B-PER
: O
but O
the O
hatter B-PER
was O
out O
of O
sight O
before O
the O
officer B-PER
could O
get O
to O
the O
door O

” O
“ O
but O
who O
is O
to O
give O
the O
prizes O
? O
” O
quite O
a O
chorus O
of O
voices O
asked O

next O
came O
an O
angry O
voice O
— O
the O
rabbit B-PER
’ O
s O
— O
“ O
pat B-PER
! O
pat B-PER
! O
where O
are O
you O
? O
” O
and O
then O
a O
voice O
she O
had O
never O
heard O
before O
, O
“ O
sure O
then O
i O
’ O
m O
here O
! O
digging O
for O
apples O
, O
yer O
honour O
! O
” O
“ O
digging O
for O
apples O
, O
indeed O
! O
” O
said O
the O
rabbit B-PER
angrily O

alice B-PER
waited O
a O
little O
, O
half O
expecting O
to O
see O
it O
again O
, O
but O
it O
did O
not O
appear O
, O
and O
after O
a O
minute O
or O
two O
she O
walked O
on O
in O
the O
direction O
in O
which O
the B-PER
march I-PER
hare I-PER
was O
said O
to O
live O

“ O
is O
that O
all O
? O
” O
said O
alice B-PER
, O
swallowing O
down O
her O
anger O
as O
well O
as O
she O
could O

first O
, O
because O
i O
’ O
m O
on O
the O
same O
side O
of O
the O
door O
as O
you O
are O
; O
secondly O
, O
because O
they O
’ O
re O
making O
such O
a O
noise O
inside O
, O
no O
one O
could O
possibly O
hear O
you O

“ O
i O
’ O
ve O
read O
that O
in O
some O
book O
, O
but O
i O
don O
’ O
t O
remember O
where O

) O
down O
, O
down O
, O
down O

she O
went O
in O
without O
knocking O
, O
and O
hurried O
upstairs O
, O
in O
great O
fear O
lest O
she O
should O
meet O
the O
real O
mary B-PER
ann I-PER
, O
and O
be O
turned O
out O
of O
the O
house B-LOC
before O
she O
had O
found O
the O
fan O
and O
gloves O

“ O
well O
, O
i O
never O
heard O
it O
before O
, O
” O
said O
the B-PER
mock I-PER
turtle I-PER
; O
“ O
but O
it O
sounds O
uncommon O
nonsense O

so O
you O
see O
, O
miss O
, O
we O
’ O
re O
doing O
our O
best O
, O
afore O
she O
comes O
, O
to O
— O
” O
at O
this O
moment O
five O
, O
who O
had O
been O
anxiously O
looking O
across O
the O
garden B-LOC
, O
called O
out O
“ O
the O
queen B-PER
! O
the O
queen B-PER
! O
” O
and O
the B-PER
three I-PER
gardeners I-PER
instantly O
threw O
themselves O
flat O
upon O
their O
faces O

he O
was O
an O
old O
crab O
, O
_he_ O
was O

“ O
it O
’ O
s O
really O
dreadful O
, O
” O
she O
muttered O
to O
herself O
, O
“ O
the O
way O
all O
the O
creatures O
argue O

” O
“ O
what O
a O
curious O
plan O
! O
” O
exclaimed O
alice B-PER

“ O
the O
trial O
cannot O
proceed O
, O
” O
said O
the O
king B-PER
in O
a O
very O
grave O
voice O
, O
“ O
until O
all O
the O
jurymen B-PER
are O
back O
in O
their O
proper O
places O
— O
_all_ O
, O
” O
he O
repeated O
with O
great O
emphasis O
, O
looking O
hard O
at O
alice B-PER
as O
he O
said O
so O

“ O
but O
perhaps O
he O
can O
’ O
t O
help O
it O
, O
” O
she O
said O
to O
herself O
; O
“ O
his O
eyes O
are O
so O
_very_ O
nearly O
at O
the O
top O
of O
his O
head O

so O
you O
see O
, O
miss O
, O
we O
’ O
re O
doing O
our O
best O
, O
afore O
she O
comes O
, O
to O
— O
” O
at O
this O
moment O
five B-PER
, O
who O
had O
been O
anxiously O
looking O
across O
the O
garden B-LOC
, O
called O
out O
“ O
the O
queen B-PER
! O
the O
queen B-PER
! O
” O
and O
the O
three B-PER
gardeners I-PER
instantly O
threw O
themselves O
flat O
upon O
their O
faces O

two B-PER
began O
in O
a O
low O
voice O
, O
“ O
why O
the O
fact O
is O
, O
you O
see O
, O
miss O
, O
this O
here O
ought O
to O
have O
been O
a O
_red_ O
rose O
- O
tree O
, O
and O
we O
put O
a O
white O
one O
in O
by O
mistake O
; O
and O
if O
the O
queen B-PER
was O
to O
find O
it O
out O
, O
we O
should O
all O
have O
our O
heads O
cut O
off O
, O
you O
know O

“ O
after O
that O
, O
” O
continued O
the O
hatter B-PER
, O
“ O
i O
cut O
some O
more O
bread O
- O
and O
- O
butter O
— O
” O
“ O
but O
what O
did O
the O
dormouse B-PER
say O
? O
” O
one O
of O
the O
jury B-PER
asked O

what O
_will_ O
become O
of O
me O
? O
” O
luckily O
for O
alice B-PER
, O
the O
little O
magic O
bottle O
had O
now O
had O
its O
full O
effect O
, O
and O
she O
grew O
no O
larger O
: O
still O
it O
was O
very O
uncomfortable O
, O
and O
, O
as O
there O
seemed O
to O
be O
no O
sort O
of O
chance O
of O
her O
ever O
getting O
out O
of O
the O
room B-LOC
again O
, O
no O
wonder O
she O
felt O
unhappy O

“ O
it O
’ O
s O
no O
use O
speaking O
to O
it O
, O
” O
she O
thought O
, O
“ O
till O
its O
ears O
have O
come O
, O
or O
at O
least O
one O
of O
them O

alice B-PER
felt O
dreadfully O
puzzled O
, O
the B-PER
hatter I-PER
’ O
s O
remark O
seemed O
to O
have O
no O
sort O
of O
meaning O
in O
it O
, O
and O
yet O
it O
was O
certainly O
english O

” O
seven O
flung O
down O
his O
brush O
, O
and O
had O
just O
begun O
“ O
well O
, O
of O
all O
the O
unjust O
things O
— O
” O
when O
his O
eye O
chanced O
to O
fall O
upon O
alice B-PER
, O
as O
she O
stood O
watching O
them O
, O
and O
he O
checked O
himself O
suddenly O
: O
the O
others O
looked O
round O
also O
, O
and O
all O
of O
them O
bowed O
low O

“ O
well O
, O
i O
’ O
d O
hardly O
finished O
the O
first O
verse O
, O
” O
said O
the B-PER
hatter I-PER
, O
“ O
when O
the B-PER
queen I-PER
jumped O
up O
and O
bawled O
out O
, O
‘ O
he O
’ O
s O
murdering O
the O
time O
! O
off O
with O
his O
head O
! O
’ O
” O
“ O
how O
dreadfully O
savage O
! O
” O
exclaimed O
alice B-PER

” O
so O
alice B-PER
got O
up O
and O
ran O
off O
, O
thinking O
while O
she O
ran O
, O
as O
well O
she O
might O
, O
what O
a O
wonderful O
dream O
it O
had O
been O

” O
however O
, O
she O
got O
up O
, O
and O
began O
to O
repeat O
it O
, O
but O
her O
head O
was O
so O
full O
of O
the B-PER
lobster I-PER
quadrille O
, O
that O
she O
hardly O
knew O
what O
she O
was O
saying O
, O
and O
the O
words O
came O
very O
queer O
indeed O
: O
— O
“ O
’ O
tis O
the O
voice O
of O
the B-PER
lobster I-PER
; O
i O
heard O
him O
declare O
, O
“ O
you O
have O
baked O
me O
too O
brown O
, O
i O
must O
sugar O
my O
hair O

will O
you O
, O
won O
' O
t O
you O
, O
will O
you O
, O
won O
' O
t O
you O
, O
will O
you O
join O
the O
dance O
? O
will O
you O
, O
won O
' O
t O
you O
, O
will O
you O
, O
won O
' O
t O
you O
, O
won O
' O
t O
you O
join O
the O
dance O
? O
” O
“ O
thank O
you O
, O
it O
' O
s O
a O
very O
interesting O
dance O
to O
watch O
, O
” O
said O
alice B-PER
, O
feeling O
very O
glad O
that O
it O
was O
over O
at O
last O
: O
“ O
and O
i O
do O
so O
like O
that O
curious O
song O
about O
the O
whiting O
! O
” O
“ O
oh O
, O
as O
to O
the O
whiting O
, O
” O
said O
the B-PER
mock I-PER
turtle I-PER
, O
“ O
they O
— O
you O
' O
ve O
seen O
them O
, O
of O
course O
? O
” O
“ O
yes O
, O
” O
said O
alice B-PER
, O
“ O
i O
' O
ve O
often O
seen O
them O
at O
dinn O
— O
” O
she O
checked O
herself O
hastily O

” O
“ O
you O
are O
old O
, O
” O
said O
the O
youth O
, O
“ O
as O
i O
mentioned O
before O
, O
and O
have O
grown O
most O
uncommonly O
fat O
; O
yet O
you O
turned O
a O
back O
- O
somersault O
in O
at O
the O
door O
— O
pray O
, O
what O
is O
the O
reason O
of O
that O
? O
” O
“ O
in O
my O
youth O
, O
” O
said O
the O
sage O
, O
as O
he O
shook O
his O
grey O
locks O
, O
“ O
i O
kept O
all O
my O
limbs O
very O
supple O
by O
the O
use O
of O
this O
ointment O
— O
one O
shilling O
the O
box O
— O
allow O
me O
to O
sell O
you O
a O
couple O
? O
” O
“ O
you O
are O
old O
, O
” O
said O
the O
youth O
, O
“ O
and O
your O
jaws O
are O
too O
weak O
for O
anything O
tougher O
than O
suet O
; O
yet O
you O
finished O
the O
goose O
, O
with O
the O
bones O
and O
the O
beak O
— O
pray O
, O
how O
did O
you O
manage O
to O
do O
it O
? O
” O
“ O
in O
my O
youth O
, O
” O
said O
his O
father O
, O
“ O
i O
took O
to O
the O
law O
, O
and O
argued O
each O
case O
with O
my O
wife O
; O
and O
the O
muscular O
strength O
, O
which O
it O
gave O
to O
my O
jaw O
, O
has O
lasted O
the O
rest O
of O
my O
life O

” O
“ O
how O
are O
you O
getting O
on O
? O
” O
said O
the B-PER
cat I-PER
, O
as O
soon O
as O
there O
was O
mouth O
enough O
for O
it O
to O
speak O
with O

” O
she O
said O
this O
last O
word O
two O
or O
three O
times O
over O
to O
herself O
, O
being O
rather O
proud O
of O
it O
: O
for O
she O
thought O
, O
and O
rightly O
too O
, O
that O
very O
few O
little O
girls O
of O
her O
age O
knew O
the O
meaning O
of O
it O
at O
all O

” O
when O
did O
you O
begin O
? O
” O
the B-PER
hatter I-PER
looked O
at O
the B-PER
march I-PER
hare I-PER
, O
who O
had O
followed O
him O
into O
the B-LOC
court I-LOC
, O
arm O
- O
in O
- O
arm O
with O
the B-PER
dormouse I-PER

at O
last O
the B-PER
mouse I-PER
, O
who O
seemed O
to O
be O
a O
person O
of O
authority O
among O
them O
, O
called O
out O
, O
“ O
sit O
down O
, O
all O
of O
you O
, O
and O
listen O
to O
me O
! O
_i O
’ O
ll_ O
soon O
make O
you O
dry O
enough O
! O
” O
they O
all O
sat O
down O
at O
once O
, O
in O
a O
large O
ring O
, O
with O
the B-PER
mouse I-PER
in O
the O
middle O

alice B-PER
did O
not O
quite O
know O
what O
to O
say O
to O
this O
: O
so O
she O
helped O
herself O
to O
some O
tea O
and O
bread O
- O
and O
- O
butter O
, O
and O
then O
turned O
to O
the B-PER
dormouse I-PER
, O
and O
repeated O
her O
question O

he O
sent O
them O
word O
i O
had O
not O
gone O
( O
we O
know O
it O
to O
be O
true O
) O
: O
if O
she O
should O
push O
the O
matter O
on O
, O
what O
would O
become O
of O
you O
? O
i O
gave O
her O
one O
, O
they O
gave O
him O
two O
, O
you O
gave O
us O
three O
or O
more O
; O
they O
all O
returned O
from O
him O
to O
you O
, O
though O
they O
were O
mine O
before O

advice O
from O
a O
caterpillar B-PER
the O
caterpillar B-PER
and O
alice B-PER
looked O
at O
each O
other O
for O
some O
time O
in O
silence O
: O
at O
last O
the O
caterpillar B-PER
took O
the O
hookah O
out O
of O
its O
mouth O
, O
and O
addressed O
her O
in O
a O
languid O
, O
sleepy O
voice O

for O
instance O
, O
suppose O
it O
were O
nine O
o O
’ O
clock O
in O
the O
morning O
, O
just O
time O
to O
begin O
lessons O
: O
you O
’ O
d O
only O
have O
to O
whisper O
a O
hint O
to O
time O
, O
and O
round O
goes O
the O
clock O
in O
a O
twinkling O
! O
half O
- O
past O
one O
, O
time O
for O
dinner O
! O
” O
( O
“ O
i O
only O
wish O
it O
was O
, O
” O
the O
march B-PER
hare I-PER
said O
to O
itself O
in O
a O
whisper O

” O
“ O
it O
is O
a O
very O
good O
height O
indeed O
! O
” O
said O
the O
caterpillar B-PER
angrily O
, O
rearing O
itself O
upright O
as O
it O
spoke O
( O
it O
was O
exactly O
three O
inches O
high O
) O

all O
the O
time O
they O
were O
playing O
the O
queen B-PER
never O
left O
off O
quarrelling O
with O
the O
other O
players O
, O
and O
shouting O
“ O
off O
with O
his O
head O
! O
” O
or O
“ O
off O
with O
her O
head O
! O
” O
those O
whom O
she O
sentenced O
were O
taken O
into O
custody O
by O
the B-PER
soldiers I-PER
, O
who O
of O
course O
had O
to O
leave O
off O
being O
arches O
to O
do O
this O
, O
so O
that O
by O
the O
end O
of O
half O
an O
hour O
or O
so O
there O
were O
no O
arches O
left O
, O
and O
all O
the O
players O
, O
except O
the O
king B-PER
, O
the O
queen B-PER
, O
and O
alice B-PER
, O
were O
in O
custody O
and O
under O
sentence O
of O
execution O

) O
“ O
all O
right O
, O
so O
far O
, O
” O
said O
the O
king B-PER
, O
and O
he O
went O
on O
muttering O
over O
the O
verses O
to O
himself O
: O
“ O
‘ O
_we O
know O
it O
to O
be O
true_ O
— O
’ O
that O
’ O
s O
the O
jury O
, O
of O
course O
— O
‘ O
_i O
gave O
her O
one O
, O
they O
gave O
him O
two_ O
— O
’ O
why O
, O
that O
must O
be O
what O
he O
did O
with O
the O
tarts O
, O
you O
know O
— O
” O
“ O
but O
, O
it O
goes O
on O
‘ O
_they O
all O
returned O
from O
him O
to O
you_ O
, O
’ O
” O
said O
alice B-PER

“ O
same O
as O
if O
he O
had O
a O
bone O
in O
his O
throat O
, O
” O
said O
the O
gryphon B-PER
: O
and O
it O
set O
to O
work O
shaking O
him O
and O
punching O
him O
in O
the O
back O

“ O
please O
, O
then O
, O
” O
said O
alice B-PER
, O
“ O
how O
am O
i O
to O
get O
in O
? O
” O
“ O
there O
might O
be O
some O
sense O
in O
your O
knocking O
, O
” O
the B-PER
footman I-PER
went O
on O
without O
attending O
to O
her O
, O
“ O
if O
we O
had O
the O
door O
between O
us O

alice B-PER
looked O
up O
, O
and O
there O
stood O
the O
queen B-PER
in O
front O
of O
them O
, O
with O
her O
arms O
folded O
, O
frowning O
like O
a O
thunderstorm O

alice B-PER
waited O
a O
little O
, O
half O
expecting O
to O
see O
it O
again O
, O
but O
it O
did O
not O
appear O
, O
and O
after O
a O
minute O
or O
two O
she O
walked O
on O
in O
the O
direction O
in O
which O
the O
march B-PER
hare I-PER
was O
said O
to O
live O

“ O
and O
just O
as O
i O
’ O
d O
taken O
the O
highest O
tree O
in O
the O
wood O
, O
” O
continued O
the O
pigeon B-PER
, O
raising O
its O
voice O
to O
a O
shriek O
, O
“ O
and O
just O
as O
i O
was O
thinking O
i O
should O
be O
free O
of O
them O
at O
last O
, O
they O
must O
needs O
come O
wriggling O
down O
from O
the O
sky O
! O
ugh O
, O
serpent O
! O
” O
“ O
but O
i O
’ O
m O
_not_ O
a O
serpent O
, O
i O
tell O
you O
! O
” O
said O
alice B-PER

“ O
what O
i O
was O
going O
to O
say O
, O
” O
said O
the O
dodo B-PER
in O
an O
offended O
tone O
, O
“ O
was O
, O
that O
the O
best O
thing O
to O
get O
us O
dry O
would O
be O
a O
caucus O
- O
race O
